



Ionut-Claudiu Leonte

Date of birth: 20/06/1998 | **Nationality:** Romanian | **Phone number:**

(+40) 727304987 (Mobile) | **Email address:** <u>leonteionut98@yahoo.com</u> | **Website:**

https://leonte-portfolio.netlify.app/ | LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/leonte-ionut-claudiu/

Whatsapp Messenger: +40727304987

Address: Strada Sebeşului, Nr.11, Bl.V, Sc.3, Et.4, Ap.62, Brăila, 810443, Brăila,

Romania (Home)

About me:

In the past: I worked at CLdN Malta Ltd as an Engine Cadet with an international team.

Now: I am a student at the IT School in the "Front-end Web Development"

course

Future goal: I look forward to working as a Front-end Web Developer.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

07/2022 - CURRENT

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER IT School

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React.js, Git

In progress to obtain the front-end web developer certification.

Field of study Computer Software Engineering

2017 - 2021 Constanța, Romania

CONSTANTA MARITIME UNIVERSITY Faculty of Naval Electromechanics

Address Constanța, Romania | Field of study Engineering | Final grade 9.00

2013 – 2017 Brăila, Romania

HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATION "Nicolae Bălcescu" National College, Brăila

Address Brăila, Romania | Field of study Mathematics - Informatics (informatics intensive) | Final grade 8.38

WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - 2022

ENGINE CADET - RO/RO SHIPS CLDN MALTA LTD.

- Had 3 trips contracts in 2021-2022 year.
- Assisting with any planned maintenance work.
- Helping to operate pump and fuel systems, distribution and electrical generating equipment, air conditioning plants, refrigeration systems, and cranes and lifts.
- Stripping engines and inspecting their components.
- Tracing out (following) the paths of oil, water or steam as they travel through the ship's systems.
- Taking note of daily logs from the equipment in the engine room.
- Taking soundings (measuring how much fluid is in a tank.)
- Helping to keep watch in the engine room.
- Cleaning, painting and greasing equipment

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office - advanced level | HTML | Github | CSS | JavaScript & jQuery junior knowledge | React.js

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ROMANIAN**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2
GERMAN	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2
FRENCH	B1	B1	B1	B1	B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Communication

Teamwork

Flexible Schedule

Easily Adaptable

Active-learning

HOBBIES

Travelling, Sports, Cars, Music, Movies, Video Gaming

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: AM
Driving Licence: B1
Driving Licence: B

PASSPORT

Yes

SEAMAN'S BOOK

Yes

• Registration number : 38860CT

CERTIFICATES

Basic Training (IMO)

1.Personal survival techniques

2.Personal safety and social responsabilities on board ships

3.Basic fire-fighting

4.Elementary first aid

• Certificate No.: 00026829

Certificate of Proficiency

• Certificate of Proficiency No.: 85208

Security awareness training & security training for seafarers with designated security duties (IMO)

• Certificate No.: 00007621

Certificate of Proficiency in Welding Technologies and Equipment

Certificate of Proficiency to perform functions, on board oil tankers and chemical tankers

Certificate of working in Confined Space